shabbyapple.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy - Shabby Apple

Privacy Policy 

Shabby Apple understands and respects your concerns about privacy and is committed to providing you with a safe online experience. The information below describes the type of information we collect, how it is used, and steps we take to protect your personally identifiable information. This policy applies only to website or phone orders. Periodically, we may update our Privacy and Security policies and encourage you to check this section for any changes.

How does Shabby Apple protect customer credit card information?

Shabby Apple has carefully selected a third-party service provider to transmit and manage credit card transactions. This third party service provider is compliant with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard ("PCI DSS") as a Level 1 service provider, the bankcard industry’s most stringent security standard. Security measures include physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards; sophisticated security monitoring tools; documented security policies; use of strong encryption for transmissions of Order Information to and from CyberSource Customers; restricted access of personally identifiable information; and periodic security audits by third party security experts.

Shabby Apple is PCI DSS compliant. We also have a policy for employees to safeguard client information designed to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, or use in any way.

Any visitors who do not want their personal information collected online are offered the opportunity to not submit such information to shabbyapple.com. We also offer the option for you to place your order by telephone or fax.

What personally identifiable information does shabbyapple.com collect and how is it used?

We collect only the client information we need to administer our business, provide superior service to our clients, and communicate information relating to our products and services we believe to be of interest to our clients.

This website collects personally identifiable information (such as name, address, telephone and fax numbers, email address, and credit card and purchase information) from visitors only when such information is voluntarily provided. That information is used to process your purchases and requests and to provide service. Information about your shopping cart choices, purchases, or requests for customer assistance may be passed along internally at Shabby Apple. Credit card and financing information also may be provided to credit card and consumer financing companies when required to process applications and transactions.

Information supplied to us, not including credit card information, is added to our client database. We may make portions of our web and phone order client list available to carefully chosen third parties to assist us in providing services to our customers. If you do not want your name made available this way, if you’ve moved, or if you would prefer not to receive catalogs or email from Shabby Apple, please call customer service at 801.590.9799 or request to be removed from our mailing list by clicking on the hyperlink provided in Shabby Apple emails.

Information further may be stored and used to better understand our clients, their needs, ways to improve our products and services, and to contact clients with offers that may be of interest to them.

What other information does Shabby Apple collect and how is it used?

This website also may collect information that could include data about your operating system, domain name, browser, and even the specific web pages on our website that you access or visit. We collect this information in the aggregate—on an anonymous basis—and may use it to evaluate the ease of use and convenience of our website and to make further improvements.

What are “cookies” and how are they used?

A “cookie” is a small amount of data sent to your browser from a website server that may be stored on your computer’s hard drive. When you visit our website, this site may store a “cookie” or similar file on your computer. This information may be used for general purposes such as providing you with more personalized service, storing your zip code, and even helping us track our website visits and traffic patterns.

Most Internet browsers allow users to exercise control over such files on their computers by blocking them, erasing them, or possibly notifying users when such a file is stored. We encourage you to refer to your Internet browser’s instructions to learn about those functions and options. 

How may I stop the use of my personally identifiable information?

Our website provides the opportunity—at any time—for you to be removed from mailing lists or to otherwise prevent the use in the future of your personally identifiable information.

Under what circumstances is personal information turned over to law enforcement agencies?

Any stored information that becomes subject to a subpoena, court order, or other request by any local, state, or federal agency will be provided to the requesting agency as deemed necessary by Shabby Apple.
